Preliminary Guide to The Thomas Hahn Chesapeake and Ohio Canal collection, 1939-1993 MS2020
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Aqueduct, undated (Box 24, Folder 146)
- Aqueduct #11 over Evitts Creek C&O Canal Cumberland, MD, undated (Box 24, Folder 147)
- Canal boat scene, undated (Box 24, Folder 148)
- Bridge or aqueduct, undated (Box 24, Folder 149)
- Aqueduct or bridge, undated (Box 24, Folder 150)
- C&O Canal - Antietam Aqueduct DEM, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 151)
- Aqueduct Apr 27, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 152)
- Aqueduct, undated (Box 24, Folder 153)
- Stone work, undated (Box 24, Folder 154)
- Conococheague Aqueduct C&O Canal Williamsport, undated (Box 24, Folder 155)
- Aqueduct, undated (Box 24, Folder 156)
- Canoe in front of aqueduct, undated (Box 24, Folder 157)
- C&O Canal: Dam #4 and Pot. R. overgrown. Canal prism in middle ground NCP 773 WDC July 11, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 158)
- Old Canal Barge Ruins WDC September 5, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 159)
- Dam 4 L-3233-54, undated (Box 24, Folder 160)
- Wood work (possibly old canal barge ruins), undated (Box 24, Folder 161)
- Old Canal Barge Ruins WDC, 09/05/1951 (Box 24, Folder 162)
- Bridge (possibly Burnside Bridge) Apr, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 163)
- Model C&O Canal boat hatches removed, undated (Box 24, Folder 164)
- Wood work in a field, undated (Box 24, Folder 165)
- Dam no. 4 May, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 166)
- Aqueduct, undated (Box 24, Folder 167)
- Aqueduct, undated (Box 24, Folder 168)
- Aqueduct, undated (Box 24, Folder 169)
- Aqueduct, undated (Box 24, Folder 170)
- Canal boat and mule near Williamsport, undated (Box 24, Folder 171)
- Dam no. 4 May, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 172)
- Aqueduct, undated (Box 24, Folder 173)
- Aqueduct, undated (Box 24, Folder 174)
- Aqueduct, undated (Box 24, Folder 175)
- Wood work (possibly old canal barge ruins), undated (Box 24, Folder 176)
- Below Lock 38 Shepherdstown, undated (Box 24, Folder 177)
- Cushwa Basin Williamsport, MD C&O Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 178)
- C&O Canal: Raleigh Benger, Sharpsburg, MD w/ barge model NCP 812 WDC, 03/23/1954 (Box 24, Folder 179)
- Violets Lock, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 180)
- Seneca Aqueduct and Lock #24 C&O Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 181)
- Sunset on the Potomac Seneca, MD, undated (Box 24, Folder 182)
- 1962 hike Point of Rocks boat ramp dedication Geo Kline - Justice Douglas, undated (Box 24, Folder 183)
- Ariel view of Great Falls Tavern area of the C&O Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 184)
- Douglas hike, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 185)
- Cushwa's coal operation at Williamsport, undated (Box 24, Folder 186)
- C&O Canal barge being pulled by mules, undated (Box 24, Folder 187)
- Round Top Kilns, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 188)
- Canal boat near Cohill Station, undated (Box 24, Folder 189)
- Outer walls and main gate, Fort Frederick, MD, near C&O Canal NCP WDC, 09/11/1946 (Box 24, Folder 190)
- Canal boat model, undated (Box 24, Folder 191)
- Canal map, undated (Box 24, Folder 192)
- Canal boats near Williamsport, undated (Box 24, Folder 193)
- Cushwa's coal operation at Williamsport, undated (Box 24, Folder 194)
- Old barge remains WDC, 09/05/1951 (Box 24, Folder 195)
- Douglas Hike, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 196)
- C&O Canal: start of Justice Douglas - Washington Post hike, Lock 72 NCP 788 WDC, 03/20/1954 (Box 24, Folder 197)
- Building and Lock on Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 198)
- Building and Lock on Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 199)
- C&O Canal: Bow view barge model NCP 813 WDC, 03/23/1954 (Box 24, Folder 200)
- C&O Canal: Model of barge with its owner, Raleigh Bender NCP 811 WDC, 03/23/1954 (Box 24, Folder 201)
- C 70 Canal field of wildflowers L-3227-70 DEM, 1943 (Box 24, Folder 202)
- Building and Lock on Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 203)
- Person on Barge, undated (Box 24, Folder 204)
- Paw Paw Tunnel, undated (Box 24, Folder 205)
- Group of people and Justice Douglas on C&O Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 206)
- Building, undated (Box 24, Folder 207)
- Wooden Flume above Edward's Ferry on the C&O Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 208)
- C&O Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 209)
- Group of people on C&O Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 210)
- Paw Paw Tunnel, undated (Box 24, Folder 211)
- C&O Canal: Note the channels caused by Tow Ropes at Lock 18 L-3227-126, undated (Box 24, Folder 212)
- Justice Douglas and other person on Douglas Hike, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 213)
- C&O Canal: barge Model Stern to Bow View NCP 816 WDC, 03/23/1954 (Box 24, Folder 214)
- Stonework over the C&O Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 215)
- Canal Horn, undated (Box 24, Folder 216)
- Canal boat, undated (Box 24, Folder 217)
- C&O Canal: Bow of old freight barge, Spring Gap W.D. Chick NCP 779 MS, 11/13/1953 (Box 24, Folder 218)
- Stonework, undated (Box 24, Folder 219)
- C&O Canal near Spring Gap, MD, undated (Box 24, Folder 220)
- Lock 75 (?), undated (Box 24, Folder 221)
- Aqueduct, undated (Box 24, Folder 222)
- Building and lock at Lock 75, undated (Box 24, Folder 223)
- Canal Basin in Cumberland, undated (Box 24, Folder 224)
- Blowing up Dam 8 at Cumberland, undated (Box 24, Folder 225)
- 10th Annual Hike C&O Canal Association Justice Douglas leads, undated (Box 24, Folder 226)
- Freight boat, undated (Box 24, Folder 227)
- Building, undated (Box 24, Folder 228)
- Group on side of building with C&O Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 229)
- Looking aft amid ships of Barge No. 57 below Hancock, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 230)
- Lock keeper's house at Lock #11, undated (Box 24, Folder 231)
- Aqueduct over Evitts Creek; near Cumberland; C Chesapeake & Ohio Canal National Monument, Maryland photo by Robert G. Johnsson, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 232)
- Stern section of Barge No. 57 below Hancock, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 233)
- C&O Canal mile marker in Washington, DC, undated (Box 24, Folder 234)
- Stop gate at Dam #4 July, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 235)
- Canal boat near Cohill station, undated (Box 24, Folder 236)
- Warehouse at Snyders Landing (?), undated (Box 24, Folder 237)
- Roundtop cement Mill above Hancock, undated (Box 24, Folder 238)
- Muskrat holes, drawdown above Dam #4, undated (Box 24, Folder 239)
- Women washing on canal boat, from: The Erie Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 240)
- Family Group in canal boat cabin, The Erie Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 241)
- Girl in boat, undated (Box 24, Folder 242)
- Lock 75, undated (Box 24, Folder 243)
- Lock 75, undated (Box 24, Folder 244)
- The Story of the C&O Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 245)
- The Old Ditch 1828-1924, undated (Box 24, Folder 246)
- Boating on the James River, undated (Box 24, Folder 247)
- Pennsylvania Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 248)
- James River view from Glasgow, VA May, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 249)
- James River and Kanawha canal at Richmond, undated (Box 24, Folder 250)
- James river and Kanawha Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 251)
- Great Falls of the Potomac, September, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 252)
- President John Adams, undated (Box 24, Folder 253)
- B&O Railroad Dedication in Baltimore 4 July, 1828 (Box 24, Folder 254)
- Canal construction, undated (Box 24, Folder 255)
- The Atlantic B&O, 1832 (Box 24, Folder 256)
- Construction of Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 257)
- Summer drawdown at Four Locks, undated (Box 24, Folder 258)
- Irish Fighting George Potter To the Golden Door, undated (Box 24, Folder 259)
- Upstream (south) portal of Paw Paw Tunnel, undated (Box 24, Folder 260)
- Berm side of Road Culvert at Four Locks, undated (Box 24, Folder 261)
- Culvert at Green Springs near McCoys Ferry, undated (Box 24, Folder 262)
- Guard Lock #3, looking downstream, 04/03/1965 (Box 24, Folder 263)
- Violets Lock (23), 1961 (Box 24, Folder 264)
- Lock 25 Edwards Ferry, undated (Box 24, Folder 265)
- C&O Canal, canal boat being towed by mules, undated (Box 24, Folder 266)
- Night Scene (not C&O), undated (Box 24, Folder 267)
- Typical C&O Canal freight boat, undated (Box 24, Folder 268)
- Canal boat in lock, undated (Box 24, Folder 269)
- Conococheague Aqueduct at Williamsport, undated (Box 24, Folder 270)
- Upstream face of Town Creek Aqueduct, undated (Box 24, Folder 271)
- The Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 272)
- Towpath near Culvert #114, undated (Box 24, Folder 273)
- Antietam Aqueduct, undated (Box 24, Folder 274)
- Conococheague Aqueduct, undated (Box 24, Folder 275)
- Lock 18 Sept, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 276)
- Hank Holland Fishing along Little Slackwater, undated (Box 24, Folder 277)
- Douglas Hike, picturing Justice Douglas, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 278)
- Lock 29 (Lander) Douglas Hike, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 279)
- Canal Routes from The Erie Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 280)
- Canal boats near Williamsport, undated (Box 24, Folder 281)
- Near Williamsport, undated (Box 24, Folder 282)
- Girl, mules and boat, undated (Box 24, Folder 283)
- Girl and mule, undated (Box 24, Folder 284)
- The End, undated (Box 24, Folder 285)
- Cushwa's coal operation at Williamsport, undated (Box 24, Folder 286)
- Williamsport at Cushwas, undated (Box 24, Folder 287)
- Stop Gate at Dam #4 July, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 288)
- James River and Kanawha Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 289)
- Boats in line during Summer drawdown at Four Locks, undated (Box 24, Folder 290)
- Boat basin at Cushwa's at Williamsport, undated (Box 24, Folder 291)
- Women washing on Canal boat from The Erie Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 292)
- Family group in canal boat cabin from The Erie Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 293)
- Mules, undated (Box 24, Folder 294)
- First packet boat from Throm. Picture History of Am. Transportation, undated (Box 24, Folder 295)
- River boat from Throm. Picture History of Transportation, undated (Box 24, Folder 296)
- Wagon team from Throm. Picture History of Am. Transportation, undated (Box 24, Folder 297)
- Packet boat on Erie Canal from The Erie Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 298)
- Boat No. 8, undated (Box 24, Folder 299)
- NY Central RR and Erie Canal near Little Falls, NY Carter: When RR's Were Now, undated (Box 24, Folder 300)
- Racing steamboats Throm: Picture History of American Transportation, undated (Box 24, Folder 301)
- Winch House at Dam 4, undated (Box 24, Folder 302)
- Blowing up Dam 8 at Cumberland, undated (Box 24, Folder 303)
- Canal boat, undated (Box 24, Folder 304)
- Canal boat No.8, undated (Box 24, Folder 305)
- Girl, mules and boat, undated (Box 24, Folder 306)
- Girl and mule, undated (Box 24, Folder 307)
- Freight boat, undated (Box 24, Folder 308)
- Packet boat on Erie Canal from The Erie Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 309)
- Fast passenger packet from Throm. Picture History of Am Transportation, undated (Box 24, Folder 310)
- Model of mules, undated (Box 24, Folder 311)
- Canal boat No. 8, undated (Box 24, Folder 312)
- NY Central RR and Erie Canal near Little Falls from: Carter: When R.Rs Were Now, undated (Box 24, Folder 313)
- Scene on the Erie Canal from: The Erie Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 314)
- Boats on canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 315)
- One of Leech and & Company's fast Pennsylvania Packets, with the horses in a trot, passing a freight boat not far from the Portage Railway, undated (Box 24, Folder 316)
- James River and Kanawha Canal at Richmond, undated (Box 24, Folder 317)
- First packet boat from Throm Picture History of American Transportation, undated (Box 24, Folder 318)
- Wilderness Road, undated (Box 24, Folder 319)
- Pack train, undated (Box 24, Folder 320)
- Wagon trains meet boatmen from Throm: Picture History of Transportation, undated (Box 24, Folder 321)
- River boat from Throm. Picture History of Transportation, undated (Box 24, Folder 322)
- Packet boat on Erie Canal from: The Erie Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 323)
- Boat No. 8, undated (Box 24, Folder 324)
- NY Central RR and Erie Canal near Little Falls. Carter: When RR's Were Now, undated (Box 24, Folder 325)
- Racing steam boats. Throm. Picture History of Am. Transportation, undated (Box 24, Folder 326)
- Canal boat, undated (Box 24, Folder 327)
- The Duke of Bridgewater's canal crossing the Irwell, undated (Box 24, Folder 328)
- Wagon train in the Rockies, from Billington The Far Western Frontier, undated (Box 24, Folder 329)
- Erie Canal scene from: The Erie Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 330)
- Probably Erie, undated (Box 24, Folder 331)
- Loading canal boat on RR car in Philadelphia (Hoffman), undated (Box 24, Folder 332)
- Pennsylvania Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 333)
- Loading canal boats on RR car in Basin of Allegheny Portage RR (Hoffman), undated (Box 24, Folder 334)
- Pulling R car with canal boat sections up Incline Allegheny Portage RR (Hoffman), undated (Box 24, Folder 335)
- Staplebend Tunnel Allegheny Portage RR (Hoffman), undated (Box 24, Folder 336)
- Lock #2, Potomac Canal, Great Falls, MD, undated (Box 24, Folder 337)
- The Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 338)
- Upstream face of Town Creek Aqueduct, undated (Box 24, Folder 339)
- Towpath near culvert #114, undated (Box 24, Folder 340)
- Antietam Aqueduct, undated (Box 24, Folder 341)
- Cononococheague Aqueduct, undated (Box 24, Folder 342)
- Destruction of Dam #8 at Cumberland, undated (Box 24, Folder 343)
- Lock, undated (Box 24, Folder 344)
- People working on C&O Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 345)
- Lock, undated (Box 24, Folder 346)
- C&O Canal and Lock, undated (Box 24, Folder 347)
- Lock at the Great Falls Tavern Lock, undated (Box 24, Folder 348)
- Winter view with duck of the Lock at Great Falls Tavern, undated (Box 24, Folder 349)
- Lock and C&O Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 350)
- Stonework building, undated (Box 24, Folder 351)
- Stonework building, undated (Box 24, Folder 352)
- Lock and C&O Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 353)
- Wooden building, undated (Box 24, Folder 354)
- Person on Lock, undated (Box 24, Folder 355)
- Canal, undated (Box 24, Folder 356)
- Lock 19, C&O Canal and towpath near Great Falls NCP WDC, 07/05/1947 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Great Falls Tavern, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Great Falls, MD Tavern, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
- People on woodwork next to the Potomac River, undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
- C&O Canal above Great Falls, undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
- C&O Canal, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Log Cabin, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
- C&O Canal barge being pulled by a mule, undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
- C&O Canal, undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Lock 7 Glen Echo, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Canal Repair Widewater, undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
- C&O Canal, undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Ruined Locktender's house Lock #16 on the C&O Canal, undated (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Wooden building, undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Stone building, undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Lock 16?, undated (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Lock and C&O Canal, undated (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Lock 23, undated (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Waterway on C&O Canal, undated (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Lock 25 Edwards Ferry in Winter, undated (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Lock 25 Edwards Ferry, undated (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Bridge across canal at Whites Ferry, undated (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Sandy Hook, Flood scene, undated (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Canal and B&O RR below Harper's Ferry, undated (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Harpers Ferry C&O Canal in foreground, 1857 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Dam 3 above Harpers Ferry, undated (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Wooden and stone structure, undated (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Wooden and stone structure, undated (Box 25, Folder 28)
- Dam, undated (Box 25, Folder 29)
- Wooden and stone structure, undated (Box 25, Folder 30)
- Wooden and stone structure, undated (Box 25, Folder 31)
- Canal boats near Williamsport, undated (Box 25, Folder 32)
- Waterway with stone structure in the distance, undated (Box 25, Folder 33)
- Waterway and bridge, undated (Box 25, Folder 34)
- Bridge or aqueduct, undated (Box 25, Folder 35)
- Waterway, undated (Box 25, Folder 36)
- Lock, undated (Box 25, Folder 37)
- C&O Canal Hancock, MD Ruins of barge, undated (Box 25, Folder 38)
- Bridge or aqueduct, undated (Box 25, Folder 39)
- Bridge or aqueduct, undated (Box 25, Folder 40)
- Ruins of stone structure C&O Canal Great Falls, MD, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 41)
- Ruins of stone structure C&O Canal Great Falls, MD, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 42)
- Ruins of stone structure C&O Canal Great Falls, MD, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 43)
- Ruins of stone structure C&O Canal Great Falls, MD, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 44)
- Ruins of stone structure C&O Canal Great Falls, MD, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 45)
- Ruins of stone structure C&O Canal Great Falls, MD, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 46)
- Ruins of stone structure C&O Canal Great Falls, MD, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 47)
- Ruins of stone structure C&O Canal Great Falls, MD, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 48)
- Ruins of stone structure C&O Canal Great Falls, MD, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 49)
- Ruins of stone structure C&O Canal Great Falls, MD, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 50)
- Ruins of stone structure C&O Canal Great Falls, MD, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 51)
- Ruins of stone structure C&O Canal Great Falls, MD, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 52)
- Ruins of stone structure C&O Canal Great Falls, MD, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 53)
- Potomac River at Great Falls, MD, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 54)
- Danger Keep Out Sign on structure Great Falls, MD, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 55)
- Lock on the C&O Canal Great Falls, MD, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 56)
- Lock on the C&O Canal Great Falls, MD, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 57)
- Lock on the C&O Canal Great Falls, MD, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 58)
- Cliffs along the C&O Canal Great Falls, MD, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 59)
- Lock on the C&O Canal Great Falls, MD, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 60)
- Potomac River at Great Falls, MD, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 61)
- Potomac River at Great Falls, MD, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 62)
- Lock on the C&O Canal Great Falls, MD, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 63)
- Lock on the C&O Canal Great Falls, MD, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 64)
- Cliffs along the C&O Canal Great Falls, MD, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 65)
- Lock on the C&O Canal Great Falls, MD, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 66)
- Lock on the C&O Canal Great Falls, MD, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 67)
- Potomac River at Great Falls, MD, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 68)
- Potomac River at Great Falls, MD, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 69)
- People walking at Great Falls, MD, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 70)
- People inspecting rock at Great Falls, MD, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 71)
- People walking in the woods with waterway at Great Falls, MD, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 72)
- People in woods at Great Falls, MD, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 73)
- Inlet Lock #3 above Harpers Ferry C&O Canal, undated (Box 25, Folder 74)
- People on rocks near rapids (probably at Great Falls, MD), undated (Box 25, Folder 75)
- Lock 33 Harpers Ferry, undated (Box 25, Folder 76)
- Canal And B&O RR below Harpers Ferry, undated (Box 25, Folder 77)
- Dam 6, undated (Box 25, Folder 78)
- Lock #54 C&O Canal, undated (Box 25, Folder 79)
- Engine House Round Top, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 80)
- Round Top (MD) Cement Plant, Later C&O Canal, undated (Box 25, Folder 81)
- Round Top (MD) Cement Plant, Later C&O Canal, undated (Box 25, Folder 82)
- Round Top (MD) Cement Plant, Early C&O Canal, undated (Box 25, Folder 83)
- Bow section of Barge No. 57 below Hancock, 1939 (Box 25, Folder 84)
- Summer drawdown at Four Locks, undated (Box 25, Folder 85)
- Lock #46 and ruins of towpath crossover bridge, undated (Box 25, Folder 86)
- Barge drawn by mules along C&O Canal, undated (Box 25, Folder 87)
- Cushwa Basin Williamsport, MD C&O Canal, undated (Box 25, Folder 88)
- C&O Canal at Williamsport, Maryland, with Cushwa's Coal and Brick Warehouse, undated (Box 25, Folder 89)
- Grist Mill at Williamsport, MD C&O Canal, undated (Box 25, Folder 90)
- C&O Canal scene near Williamsport, MD, undated (Box 25, Folder 91)
- Lock 41 C&O Canal, undated (Box 25, Folder 92)
- Winch House at Dam 4, undated (Box 25, Folder 93)
- Snyders Landing C&O Canal, undated (Box 25, Folder 94)
- Lock 38 C&O Canal, undated (Box 25, Folder 95)
- Lock 38 (Sheperdstown Lock) C&O Canal, undated (Box 25, Folder 96)
- Lock House at Lock 38 C&O Canal, undated (Box 25, Folder 97)
- C&O Canal scene below Lock 38, Shepherdstown, WV, with the Norfolk & Western Railroad Bridge, undated (Box 25, Folder 98)
- Stone structures in water, undated (Box 25, Folder 99)
- Below Lock 38, Shepherdstown, undated (Box 25, Folder 100)
- Bridge, undated (Box 25, Folder 101)
- Stonework, undated (Box 25, Folder 102)
- Lime Plant near Lime Kiln Road, C&O Canal, undated (Box 25, Folder 103)
- Drawing of buildings of Shenandoah City, WV - from a drawing by Leonard Harbagge, engineer Shenandoah Navigation, 1808 ca. (Box 25, Folder 104)
- Drawing of buildings of Shenandoah City, WV - from a drawing by Leonard Harbagge, engineer Shenandoah Navigation, 1808 ca. (Box 25, Folder 105)
- Drawing of buildings of Shenandoah City, WV - from a drawing by Leonard Harbagge, engineer Shenandoah Navigation, 1808 ca. (Box 25, Folder 106)
- Drawing of buildings of Shenandoah City, WV - from a drawing by Leonard Harbagge, engineer Shenandoah Navigation, 1808 ca. (Box 25, Folder 107)
- Drawing of buildings of Shenandoah City, WV - from a drawing by Leonard Harbagge, engineer Shenandoah Navigation, 1808 ca. (Box 25, Folder 108)
- Drawing of buildings of Shenandoah City, WV - from a drawing by Leonard Harbagge, engineer Shenandoah Navigation, 1808 ca. (Box 25, Folder 109)
- Drawing of buildings of Shenandoah City, WV - from a drawing by Leonard Harbagge, engineer Shenandoah Navigation, 1808 ca. (Box 25, Folder 110)
- Drawing of buildings of Shenandoah City, WV - from a drawing by Leonard Harbagge, engineer Shenandoah Navigation, 1808 ca. (Box 25, Folder 111)
- Drawing of buildings of Shenandoah City, WV - from a drawing by Leonard Harbagge, engineer Shenandoah Navigation, 1808 ca. (Box 25, Folder 112)
- Drawing of buildings of Shenandoah City, WV - from a drawing by Leonard Harbagge, engineer Shenandoah Navigation, 1808 ca. (Box 25, Folder 113)
- Drawing of buildings of Shenandoah City, WV - from a drawing by Leonard Harbagge, engineer Shenandoah Navigation, 1808 ca. (Box 25, Folder 114)
- Drawing of buildings of Shenandoah City, WV - from a drawing by Leonard Harbagge, engineer Shenandoah Navigation, 1808 ca. (Box 25, Folder 115)
- Drawing of buildings of Shenandoah City, WV - from a drawing by Leonard Harbagge, engineer Shenandoah Navigation, 1808 ca. (Box 25, Folder 116)
- Drawing of buildings of Shenandoah City, WV - from a drawing by Leonard Harbagge, engineer Shenandoah Navigation, 1808 ca. (Box 25, Folder 117)
- Drawing of buildings of Shenandoah City, WV - from a drawing by Leonard Harbagge, engineer Shenandoah Navigation, 1808 ca. (Box 25, Folder 118)
- Drawing of buildings of Shenandoah City, WV - from a drawing by Leonard Harbagge, engineer Shenandoah Navigation, 1808 ca. (Box 25, Folder 119)
- Drawing of buildings of Shenandoah City, WV - from a drawing by Leonard Harbagge, engineer Shenandoah Navigation, 1808 ca. (Box 25, Folder 120)
- Drawing of buildings of Shenandoah City, WV - from a drawing by Leonard Harbagge, engineer Shenandoah Navigation, 1808 ca. (Box 25, Folder 121)
- Drawing of buildings of Shenandoah City, WV - from a drawing by Leonard Harbagge, engineer Shenandoah Navigation, 1808 ca. (Box 25, Folder 122)
- Drawing of buildings of Shenandoah City, WV - from a drawing by Leonard Harbagge, engineer Shenandoah Navigation, 1808 ca. (Box 25, Folder 123)
- Drawing of buildings of Shenandoah City, WV - from a drawing by Leonard Harbagge, engineer Shenandoah Navigation, 1808 ca. (Box 25, Folder 124)
- Drawing of buildings of Shenandoah City, WV - from a drawing by Leonard Harbagge, engineer Shenandoah Navigation, 1808 ca. (Box 25, Folder 125)
- Bingley 5-rise Locks Leeds and Liverpool Canal - England, undated (Box 25, Folder 126)
- Bingley - England, undated (Box 25, Folder 127)
- Islington Tunnel Regents Canal London England, undated (Box 25, Folder 128)
- Regents Canal England, undated (Box 25, Folder 129)
- Regents Canal England, undated (Box 25, Folder 130)
- River Lea England, undated (Box 25, Folder 131)
- River Lea England, undated (Box 25, Folder 132)